A blood bath.
一场血战
- Who's behind it?   - I didn't see anyone I recognize.
- 是谁操纵的   - 我没有看到认识的
Maybe one...
或许有一个
I know his face. He's local, Riley Biers.
我认得他   他是本地人 Riley Biers
He didn't start this.
但不是他发动的
Whoever did is staying out of the action.
始作俑者并没有参与此次行动
They must be playing with the blind spots in your vision.
他们肯定是在利用你的幻象盲点
Either way, the army is coming...
总之 吸血鬼军队即将到来...
and there aren't enough of us to protect the town.
我们不够人手来保护镇子
Hold up! What damn army?
等等   什么鬼军队?
- Newborns. Our kind.   - What are they after?
- 新生儿 我们吸血鬼种族 - 他们在找什么
They were passing around Bella's scent. A red blouse.
他们在传递着沾有Bella气味的东西 一件红色衬衫
They're after Bella?
他们想抓Bella?
- What the hell does this mean?   - It means an ugly fight.
- 这意味着什么?   - 意味着要开战了
With lives lost.
生灵涂炭